http://www.bdhc.org.uk/privacy-policy

HomeWalks/ACTIVITIESBLOGJOINABOUTAbout BDHCMembers' AchievementsJoin the ClubCommitteeClub RulesConstitutionMountain ThymeSafetyUseful LinksClub HistoryContact×MENUBDHC Privacy PolicyOur Privacy PolicyUpdated 30 October 2018IntroductionThis policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users (visitors to the website), the website and website owners (Blairgowrie & District Hill Walking Club). Furthermore, the way we process, stores and protect users data and information will also be detailed within this policy.The websiteThis website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies with all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.Use of cookiesWhat are cookies?Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.What do we use cookies for?We may use cookies to remember personal settings you have chosen at our website. In no other context do we use cookies to collect information that identifies you personally. Most of the cookies we set are automatically deleted from your computer when you leave our website or shortly afterwards.We use anonymous session cookies (short-term cookies that disappear when you close your browser) to help you navigate the website and make the most of the features. If you log into the website, application or a course as a registered user, your session cookie will also contain your user ID so that we can check which services you are allowed to access. They are also used to manage your shopping cart.This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.Should users wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website onto their computer’s hard drive, they should take necessary steps within their web browser’s security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.Personal informationWhilst using our website or services you may be required to provide personal information (name, address, email, details, etc.). We will use this information to provide our services for you. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679, as adopted into law of the United Kingdom in the Data Protection Act 2018. Further, by providing telephone and email details, you consent to Blairgowrie & District Hill Walking Club contacting you using that method. You have the right at any time to request a copy of the personal information we hold on you. Should you wish to receive a copy of this, or would like to be removed from our database, please contact us at sec@bdhc.org.uk.Data we may hold, why we hold it and what we do with itWebsite formsBlairgowrie & District Hill Walking Club will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information, gathered as a result of filling out the contact form on the site to anyone.We may collect the following information:First name, last name and email address.Address.Why:We will use your information as part of our club membership process.What we do:We will use the information to provide our membership services for you and to keep in touch with you – we deem these legitimate reasons to hold your information and by contracting with us you agree to us holding these details. We do not share your data with any third party unless specifically detailed in your contract.Review/RectifyYou can request access to see the information we hold on you and you can ask us to correct it it by emailing sec@bdhc.org.uk.RemovalWe are required to retain accounting information for at least 6 years to satisfy HMRC requirements. You can ask us to remove your information by emailing sec@bdhc.org.uk and we will confirm your removal by email reply and retain your email and confirmation as a record of deletion.Privacy Policy ReviewPlease note, we are routinely reviewing how we process and protect data. Therefore, changes to our policy may occur at any time. We will endeavour to publicise any changes and make you aware. This process will be reviewed at least quarterly and when there is a change to the process/procedures.Stay in TouchThank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the formBlairgowrie & District Hillwalking Club.PrivacyContact
